

#### CONTACT

Almaty, Kazakhstan

+7 (775) 976-41-65

in Link to the LinkedIn

Link to the GitHub

✓ Telegram - <u>voung\_flovver</u>

#### **ABOUT ME**

Creative Front-end developer with knowledge of React.js. Have analytical skills, so quick and independent decision-making is my thing. I can organize and plan work on time and use every minute to my advantage. I take my job very seriously and can work both individually and in a team. The ability to communicate with people of all ages and backgrounds provides me with quality relationships with colleagues. I may not be that experienced, but I am someone you will want to meet and work with. Passion for self-improvement, professional development and growth helps me find myself in any circle. I love learning new things and broadening my horizons.

#### **TARGET**

Getting a permanent job in your company. To work honestly and conscientiously in accordance with the objectives of the company to achieve the set goals.

### **LANGUAGES**

- Kazakh Native (C2)
- Russian Fluent (C1)
- English <u>Upper Intermediate</u> (B2)
- Turkish Upper Intermediate (B2) Chinese <u>Conversant</u> (A2)

#### **SKILLS**

- React.js, Next.js, HTML5, CSS3 (Less, SASS), JavaScript, Bootstrap, jQuery;
- Java, C++, Python;
- MySQL, Oracle PL/SQL, R;
- Pandas, Matplotlib, NumPy, Seaborn; Adobe Photoshop / After Effects /
- Premiere Pro, iMovie, VN:
- Git, VS Code, IntelliJ IDEA, Sublime text, Cisco Packet Tracer, Tinkercad, Anaconda, Jupyter, DOSBox, Little Man Computer, Asana;
- Figma, Canva, Corel Draw, Fusion 360°;
- Docker, Jira;
- Agile, Scrum, Kanban;

# **ACHIEVEMENTS**

- 2nd place in the Olympiad in Math (2013)
- 1st place in the Regional Olympiad in Informatics (2017)
- 2nd place in International Competition *"Infomatrix"* (2018)
- Euler Olympiad in Mathematics (2018)
- 5.5 band in IELTS (2018)
- Red Diploma of secondary education (2019)
- 3rd place in film festival "FilmFest 2022" (2022)

# **Zhassulan Serikuly**

# Frontend Developer

#### **EXPERIENCE**



June, 2021 - August, 2021 / 3 months

Atyrau, Kazakhstan

Role: IT Specialist

Responsibilities: Computer diagnostics to investigate issues, as well as to provide technical assistance and support. Fixed problems related to the computer software and hardware operation. Experience with social media and communication platforms.

Recommendation from my boss

TechnoPark SDU

September, 2021 - February, 2022 / 6 months

Almaty, Kazakhstan

Role: Frontend Developer

Tech stack: HTML, CSS, JavaScript

Responsibilities: Wrote supporting code for web applications and websites. Creating a web page based on design layouts, that is, layout using HTML and CSS. Binding to the user interface of scripts that provide visualization and animation of the site pages. Providing the required level of UI and UX.

Athena Plus

August, 2022 - December, 2022 / 5 months

Almaty, Kazakhstan

Role: Junior Frontend Developer Tech stack: React.js, Next.js

Responsibilities: Building the front-end of new projects and modernization of already finished ones. Implementation of user interface design with react framework. Optimization and increasing the functionality of UI/UX, by creating reusable code. Making some logos and animations for websites. Linking the frontend and backend of the site. Recommendation from my boss

#### **PERSONAL PROJECTS**

#### **New Navat**

Tech stack: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery

Description: Multilingual site of the new, sensational, fifth point of Teahouse Navat, which is located in the city of Almaty. Website is unusual in that each page block is the same size, allowing for the benefits of snap scrolling.

https://newnavat.netlify.app

#### **Midas Event**

Tech stack: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery

Description: A company that organizes various kinds of events. Famous for the organization of the show program in the "NEBO" and the concert of Irina Kairatovna. Each part of the site has its own unusual animation.

https://midasevent.kz

#### "YEK MAPKET"

Tech stack: Next.js

Description: Multi-page site written in next.js. The hardest part of this site is the large number of modals and forms. This company is engaged in consultations, design, sale of equipment, installation and adjustment of security systems, warranty and post-warranty service, technical support.

https://github.com/zhassulaan/check-market

## "Альпинист Товаров"

Tech stack: React.js

Description: The Alpinist-Products online store, known as yaq, is a network of multi-brand sports stores offering equipment for outdoor activities, hiking, trekking, skyrunning, running and other sports and outdoor activities. The React framework was used to implement this site. This project has a rather complex filtering point where the user can search for goods by category, by color, by gender, by size, by type, and sort the goods as they wish.

https://github.com/zhassulaan/yaq

#### **Portfolio**

GPA:

Faculty:

GPA:

Speciality:

Tech stack: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery

Description: Portfolio web-page that introduces me. This project is made to show my abilities and information, such as education, skills and work experience. Thanks to this page, you don't have to download a PDF file and read boring text on one text file. https://zhassulaan.github.io/Portfolio

#### **EDUCATION & CERTIFICATES**

Name of school/institution: Bilim-Innovation Lyceum (KTL) Location: Atyrau, Kazakhstan

Period: 2014 - 2019 5.0 / 5

Suleyman Demirel University (SDU) Name of school/institution: Location: Kaskelen, Almaty, Kazakhstan

2019 - 2023 Graduation year:

"Engineering and Natural Sciences"

Information Systems

3.26 / 4

HTML, CSS, and Javascript for Web Developers (Coursera) May 2021 Front-End Web Development with React (Coursera) April 2022